// all questions
const questions = [
    {
        "question": "What is the approximate population of Ethiopia in 2022?",
        "a": "75 million",
        "b": "152 million",
        "c": "120 million",
        "d": "250 million",
        "answer": "c"
    }, {
        "question": "How many Ethiopian heritages are registered by UNESCO?",
        "a": "12",
        "b": "4",
        "c": "17",
        "d": "9",
        "answer": "d"
    }, {
        "question": "Which scripts match the plural form of the word Welcome in Ge'ez?",
        "a": "እንጀራ በወጥ",
        "b": "አብይ አህመድ",
        "c": "እንኻን ደህና መጡ።",
        "d": "ኢትዮጵያ",
        "answer": "c"
    }, {
        "question": "How many languages are spoken in Ethiopia?",
        "a": "75-86",
        "b": "10-14",
        "c": "6-10",
        "d": "30-35",
        "answer": "a"
    }, {
        "question": "The highest and the lowest point in Ethiopia are called Ras Dejen and Afar Depression respectively. \nRas Dejen is ________meters above from sea level and Afar Depression is ________ meters below sea level?",
        "a": "1,200 and 76",
        "b": "4,620 and 125",
        "c": "5,500 and 30",
        "d": "3750 and 100",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "question": "Which agricultural product was first harvested in Ethiopia?",
        "a": "Sunflower Seeds",
        "b": "Peanuts",
        "c": "Coffee Beans",
        "d": "Vanilla Beans",
        "answer": "c"
    }, {
        "question": "Which Ethiopian emperor inspired the creation of the Rastafarian religion?",
        "a": "Fasilides",
        "b": "Haile Selassie",
        "c": "Menelik I",
        "d": "Yohannes IV",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "question": "Ethiopia was occupied by which European power during the 1930s?",
        "a": "France",
        "b": "Italy",
        "c": "Spain",
        "d": "Portugal",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "question": "The majority of Ethiopians practice which religion?",
        "a": "Hinduism",
        "b": "Islam",
        "c": "Rastafarianism",
        "d": "Christianity",
        "answer": "d"
    }, {
        "question": "What type of calendar do Ethiopians follow?",
        "a": "Gregorian",
        "b": "Coptic",
        "c": "Julian",
        "d": "Lunar",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "question": "What is the name of Ethiopia's currency?",
        "a": "Metical",
        "b": "Birr",
        "c": "Shekel",
        "d": "Pula",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "question": "Which country broke away from Ethiopia and became independent in 1993?",
        "a": "Somalia",
        "b": "Eritra",
        "c": "Chad",
        "d": "Djibouti",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "question": "Ethiopia is Africa's top exporter of this product:",
        "a": "Flour",
        "b": "Wheat",
        "c": "Corn",
        "d": "Sesame Seeds",
        "answer": "d"
    }, {
        "question": "Which town in Ethiopia is famous for its rock-hewn churches.",
        "a": "Gondar",
        "b": "Lalibela",
        "c": "Addis Ababa",
        "d": "Aksum",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "question": "Injera, a staple of the Ethiopian diet, is a type of what?",
        "a": "Vegetable",
        "b": "Bread",
        "c": "Meat",
        "d": "Soup",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "question": "What is the official language of Ethiopia?",
        "a": "Amharic",
        "b": "Arabic",
        "c": "Ethiopian",
        "d": "Swahili",
        "answer": "a"
    }, {
        "question": "What is the capital of Ethiopia?",
        "a": "Gondar",
        "b": "Lalibela",
        "c": "Addis Ababa",
        "d": "Aksum",
        "answer": "c"
    }, {
        "question": "What does the Green color in the flag represent?",
        "a": "Peace",
        "b": "Hope, Justice, and Equality",
        "c": "Sacrifice for Freedom and Equality",
        "d": "Labour, Development, and Fertility",
        "answer": "d"
    }, {
        "question": "What does the Yellow color in the flag represent?",
        "a": "Peace",
        "b": "Hope, Justice, and Equality",
        "c": "Sacrifice for Freedom and Equality",
        "d": "Labour, Development, and Fertility",
        "answer": "b"
    }, {
        "question": "What does the Red color in the flag represent?",
        "a": "Peace",
        "b": "Hope, Justice, and Equality",
        "c": "Sacrifice for Freedom and Equality",
        "d": "Labour, Development, and Fertility",
        "answer": "c"
    }, {
        "question": "What does the Blue color in the flag represent?",
        "a": "Peace",
        "b": "Hope, Justice, and Equality",
        "c": "Sacrifice for Freedom and Equality",
        "d": "Labour, Development, and Fertility",
        "answer": "a"
    }
];